If you don't know how to eat
belly dance very well, you can record it,
put your phone on record.
Life,
we'll freeze the people in front. Make sure
you have some kind of
heat in front. There's a special
system for people in the back, it's hot in the front, it's
cold.
10.
If you don't record, just turn off
your phone.
We'll all do a good, long
meditation. Meditation, lion dance.
Someone was sleeping during Lam-rim,
so I've given some explanations, and
we can take a break. Don't just
clear your nose and a napkin if
anyone needs one.
You'll find yourself at the same time. This is a quote to do,
and so let's go. Eat
dance. It begins with
tracking sounds in the room:
air conditioning, maybe heaters, a
refrigerator, the noise of cars outside the window, children's
noise,
Vita, small noises in the room. If you're in a
cottage near the Diamond Mountains and it's too
quiet, you can use the sound of air
touching your eardrums,
attaching it to your consciousness. These sounds are also present.
If you want to meditate for about half an
hour or 40 minutes, you can
do 10 breathing cycles for each of these steps.
If you're doing a meteorite for about an hour, then you can do it for
each step.  20 breathing cycles for
the first 8 levels of the lion dance
meditation concern is to
compare
each next level with the previous one in
search of the quietest one. This is freedom like cha
in the sense that you leave a
louder level and move to a
quieter one. First, direct all consciousness to the
noise of the
air conditioner and you consider the first
level of the forum, which we compare with the
beating of a heart and you compare these two with each
other and this comparison
affects you. Thus, we compare a
louder place with a quieter place.
We consciously choose a quieter place
and move our consciousness to this zone. We
compare the air conditioner, which
represents the sphere of desires, that is, roughly, the
place in which we live. We compare
you to be sick with a quiet one and choose a quieter place.
This is our heartbeat
and now we move our
consciousness to the heartbeat and this is the first
level of the forum sphere. This is not actually the
sphere of forms.
If you focus only on
the heartbeat
during your life, then
you will be born in the first level of the
sphere of forms. This is very similar to
superheroes like spiderman or
superwoman, for a post about which the
origins will end, use this
debit card.
In ninety-nine percent of cases, you always
go to more niches and
rebirths,
so we don’t want to direct all our
meditation only to silence. We want to
add certain content there
that opposes our
innate tendency to see things as the most
existing.
But to get to this zone, we
need to move up this staircase into
greater and greater silence, but not get off
on the first eight floors.
We don’t devote our lives to meditation,
just on silence. This does not stop the
aging process of dying. And so now
we focus on the heartbeat. This is the first
sphere. Level 1 of the forum.
If your creation is distracted back by the
sound of the
air conditioner, it is simply used as the
next step. Focus again,
glue your consciousness to this sound,
and then take a step back to your
heartbeat. So in this system of
meditation from healing can be
used to move from the box
to the next level. And so the
next level of forms we move the
guardian to observe the heart from the outside. We
enter the heartbeat. Technically speaking, we
move with the ve  Trades and an even higher
level of silence, an even deeper
level.
Imagine that you are inside a heart, like in a
small room, and a
heartbeat is happening around you. Maybe you
are beating inside the heart
now. You have plunged inside the heart. This is an even
quieter place than
the heartbeat outside. With each next
step we plunge into a quieter
place. The
third level of reforms is plastic.
We leave any emotional or
social attachment to prose,
meditation,
and in general, we leave any national
attachment to anything. I imagine
how the heart beats a little ahead of me, in
such a vacuum, and this does not
apply to me at all. It beats on its own,
a little ahead, and the feeling of oneself is much
smaller here. First of all, there is practically no nationality.
Set the heartbeat in a vacuum, first
of all, nationality, but you are not
connected to it in any way.
It just beats. This is the
deeper silence
than being inside the heart. The
fourth level of sulfur. The forum
is characterized by high 1 precise
concentration.
We turn off all extraneous things.
Your body felt as if it were completely
anesthetized, but you do not feel it, and
consciousness is very sharply concentrated on
one point. Imagine a very
tiny and, on the contrary, consciousness is on this, and
this helps.  Focus very strongly,
we use a grain of
sugar at the fourth level of the sphere forum, a
small grain of sugar that floats in
the darkness, a
white crystal is beautiful, and direct your
consciousness inside this grain and leave
any feelings about your body.
This is not an antidote to the king's axon. This will not solve
your problems, life's problems,
not with your work, family, and whale, or the
big problem of your mortality in general.
But you are now climbing the stairs
instead of where we will deal with these
problems.
Now we are moving to level 1 for
soon. If you will only be a maker for
this for a long period in this
life, you will be reborn together in
which there is no gross suffering.
You don't even have a
gross body. You want to live like this for many
years.
And when you die, you are always reborn in
lower worlds because you
used your good karma,
therefore, there are no places left. In this
meditation, you are simply used to
moving on. We are
flexible. Meditation can
move lemon from a single grain of sugar to a
state of consciousness that
extends throughout space.
Therefore, we imagine a huge lake and
our consciousness is similar to the surface of this
lake. This
is an immobile horizontal plane,
and this is a wave.  spreads in all
directions and we throw
with
we throw a grain into the center of this lake
and waves will begin to
diverge in all directions, this
absolute happens in absolute
silence and this is a wave several centimeters
high, 7 meters and in absolute
silence it
spreads in all directions
and this shows our flexibility when we
can transfer consciousness from 1 final
concentration to spread it over the entire
width of the universe and at the same time
remain absolutely in silence and
now observe this wave that
spreads across this lake,
it does not stop if you lose
your focus turn your consciousness to
this wave and it spreads
endlessly to the right hand of the shore
it never stops
now return back to the center of your
consciousness I three times as a dark point in the
center of the room about 2 meters above the
ground and now immerse yourself in the center of your
consciousness and we will go to an even
quieter place called the second
level of the sphere without a forum for us
and we will imagine how we turn on the
light
and the light spreads from this bulb
and it spreads in all directions
wider and wider and this color is not white  for
yellow it is pure clear light and it is not the same as the
clerk of clear light which is in
Buddhism lunch
it is just clear light crystal clear
light we imagine it as it
spreads from a single
small point
I imagine it as the page code throughout the entire
earth
then throughout the solar system reaches the
stars and further goes in this universe an
infinite number of planets
somewhere now there are people who have the letter
it then and us in many places an
infinite number of places does not
meditate on the level the second level of
the sphere without forms and I like to deliver
how my sphere of crystal light
intersects with their sphere of crystal
light
somehow we touch each other
maybe someday we will know about it
when I cook I will say let's go turn on this
flash of light and let this
crystal light spread
endlessly in all directions and this
light from your your
consciousness yours and so let's go do
not let them settle down to push
further and further and at the same
time try to become even
quieter inside
than during what we did in the
lake the
third level service for this is 7 whims
but on  The eighth level, if we consider
the air conditioner and the response, this is what we are, we
just try to imagine that we
turn off consciousness like switches. There are no
thoughts, not from these feelings, some
awareness,
just from the topic, as if your
consciousness is either and when I say let's go,
just turn off consciousness from if a thought
comes, I feel memories, just like
children, to the side, keep consciousness
turned off, even more quietly than during the
expansion, the
time of the second sphere without form, and so we
went, the
fourth level of the sphere without thief and the
highest of the 8 levels of meditation
that we use to
prepare our consciousness, the edges of
meditation, so this is 8, these eight are not
real meditation, this is just stretching
consciousness, warming up, warming up in consciousness for
real meditation, this is not yet vegetation
and cementation will not really help your life
at the fourth level of the sphere for your
previous consciousness, and the reason when
knowledge comes is also
memories, feelings, you just remain with
them, we allow them to move through
consciousness, we do not make
noise in an attempt to stop this thought, and so
we did at the last level, this is an absolutely
quiet place in which you simply give up,
we try to turn off our consciousness, but
if  It doesn't turn off, just let it go,
we remain in complete silence, and so there we
go,
now take three deep
breaths in and out, don't open your eyes,
now Marat, take your eyes and stretch,
and so the microphone, if there are any questions about
this, part of the ink, how long will we start the second
part, maybe Keith, the question is in this
first part, thank you, I was taken aback
when we move from one form to another
form, our consciousness at what level does it
stop, it's empty when I
say instructions,
should we move immediately or should we
wait, the reasons for which I give
instructions are that in order for you to learn the tour, the
tation on when you do it yourself, a
week
is used, a recording after the first recording,
and after that you can stop
using the recording, you just
move to each level, this is what the
process is, the point is to compare, you
check the level at which they
gave it now, quietly, good, I can be even quieter, you
kind of anticipate the next level,
this will be even quieter, the
food should be so emotional,
officially, the feeling of immersion even deeper,
and for me it's like drilling into the depths,
that is, in the silence, you
get used to this silence and let's go from
yours  Can I go even more quietly and here you are
immersing yourself so inside? In
fact, when you listen to the recordings, you
cannot go through the
spheres of desire because you are listening to the
voice. I think what needs to be said is that
you need to
practice a lot to come to the
meditation of the spheres without a forum. Now I am
describing when you feel real
meditation, you will understand something in
fact much deeper, so you need to
practice it like playing football or
learning a new language. It takes time and you
need to practice every day. We have now
done about an hour,
but if he cannot do an hour every
day, you can do it. Go through
these, it seems, faster. You need to go to
work and do it faster. 35
exhalations for each level. When I say
5 exhalations, first count 5, then
move, and subsequently it becomes a
distraction, but you will get used to this
time. Bring your breath for 30 minutes at 20
minutes. This hour of Pripyat exhales from 20 minutes.
So, at first,
use your breath to count, but
subsequently you will need to
free yourself from this because it also
creates noise. All sorts of other questions
[music]
Thank you, Teshila, for your teachings. During the
training, my self-awareness, as a student, is
thinking about something that they dive deep into, and
especially at the first eight levels, there is a
tendency. I force creation to think,
and it turns out that I try to
turn off consciousness, then it starts to think.
The teacher is bothering me, and I am very
upset and very tired.
My consciousness is trying to analyze
something, and I want, as it turns out, what are you sick with in
great silence. How do you
advise coping with this
state? At the very beginning, a
person's consciousness is very active,
so forcing consciousness to serve you is such a
struggle. From them, on meditation,
who wrote the best book about
meditation, Kamala Shila, he wrote three
books in Tibetan.
We read them
together in the first two years, while there was little
sewing, there is nothing in these books that
you don't go to scrap time, Lam Rim leaves
these letters of books, in these books they say
very often, I am a student, clans approach and
say that at 100, how did you become, I am
very situation, my consciousness has become much
worse, not my consciousness used to be quiet
when  Once upon a time now when I started
meditating with
noise, the creation became even worse than it was
before and in the gamma rim in mit according to the
instructions for meditation it is said
that your sony was always in such a bad
condition, you just didn’t know about it now
you listen to it and that’s why it’s so bad, it’s so
hard for you and that’s why if it’s like this the
first 6 months when you
feel that your creation has become
noisier, in fact, just learn
to listen to it for the first time in your life, in
fact, everything is so bad, it’s always been so
bad with your consciousness, the question is, you never
noticed this because you were in
this process and you didn’t learn to observe it,
therefore, being in consciousness,
being in thoughts and learning to observe
consciousness are different processes and all our
lives we were in our thoughts, very very
busy, very busy talking, now we are
learning to observe this and we say
that
everything has only gotten worse, in fact,
the question is learned to listen
and after this, not through listening, you
learn to control from the night
there are stages at which it is very exhausting
when you fight with your consciousness
actively, my recommendation would be that
you simply don’t, this did not solve the inspiration to
quickly pass through  Eight stages,
go to the ninth, the goal of completing these 8
levels is to build and
strengthen your muscles. I give you a
meditation in any way about the fact that your
consciousness is like a not very
educated dog and which
attacks you on a leash. We have a very
active
black dog that always wants to
run away somewhere. That little
dog will pull you forward and
you need to grab this dog. The dog
wants to think about winning, in my case
forever. I think about some kind of
food. Maybe you have some other
tendency
to think about a quarrel with your husband or about
how someone criticized you on the Internet.
You need to pull
the dog back a little with the leash
and it flows a little for a
while and then it starts to
rush forward again and you pull the
leash again and return it to its place.
Every time you fight with this
dog in order to bring it back,
your muscle grows and in Buddhism, exhaustion
is good, but fighting is good, it
exhausts, but this is good, but surrendering to
this process
is bad for
those who go through a three-year  retreat they
can say that this is a struggle, this is a battle
and someone later
came to my cottage
after a three-year retreat looked
inside and rock how quietly that and ichimoku
answers yes, as quietly as in the
Vietnam War,
it seems that it is quiet, but in fact, if
you really do meditation
and observe your consciousness, this war is
possible if you do it wrong, then
it looks like something quiet, but in
fact it is a real struggle and so you
need to fight every second of the struggle with
your consciousness is a struggle, but if you
go into oblivion, I'm in the area, everything is so
great, I don't think about anything,
there is a name for this, it's called subtle
thinking, clouding, if you very often
fall into this state,
it will be bad for your meditation,
so there is no need, no need to wash immediately for a
long time, although meditation in the tradition will be
sky,
traditionally we begin to
meditate for 12 minutes, then perhaps you
can move on to 20 minutes, but if you
immediately start two hours just being like this, then
you will definitely
slide into a state that is
harmful to your meditation,
what is good meditation, this is
Just like when you watch
Guardians of the Galaxy, you first watch it
with popcorn.
You watch the war of childhood. There's a
green
woman fighting, a big guy
fighting, a small tree running around.
Everyone's fighting. You eat popcorn, and there's that
special moment
when the green
woman kisses and kisses a handsome guy for
two hours. They sit there eating popcorn, like
in an American movie, and then
suddenly they start getting closer to
each other,
and it still doesn't stop,
and everyone's waiting for the shackles to finally kiss. Maybe he'll finally
kiss after two episodes. Finally,
they're getting closer, getting closer,
if they didn't forget about the popcorn. That's the
trick. That moment
in the movie. All two or three hundred people are like that, that
feeling of a good movie. That's
meditation. That's what
you want. It's not just
relaxation. In fact, 99 percent of
people who meditate dominate. That's how
meditation actually is. It's a
very sharp, pure, happy,
involved,
bright, kiss, kiss, hoopoe, if you
meditate like that.  then you are forming a
bad habit, you are harming your
consciousness and harming your future,
so
imitate a lot of wind, take a break for 20 minutes
and then come back
when you become stronger,
then you can meditate more, but you don't
need to meditate too much at the very
beginning, just wasting your time in vain
and you are forming a bad habit which is
very difficult to change later. Some other
questions:
sometimes when I meditate I see things
very frightening,
I don't scare myself that I need to take a
break, is this normal or how can I
deal with this? Level 10, 3 is dedicated to
meditation and myself, and 3 is also dedicated to
meditation and a big breakthrough in how
Jung Oppa explained meditation and a huge
breakthrough that Zinc made, which is
written in a letter from Gavan Drac. In this
letter, he told him that meditation is a
seed that opens up in your
consciousness every second where you hear
your thought in your consciousness, these seeds
open up in your consciousness, we will do it
now in meditation, a small thought
opens up in our consciousness and
you are not a thinker but a listener when you
hear your thoughts in your consciousness all day
about just a witness, you are not  Tell me
why because he is no longer here to speak
and now, minutes ago,
it is like the light that comes from a star, the
light from the star that you saw last
night, the incredibly beautiful light that you
see, the new moon, this light was a hundred years ago
and was lowered, by the time this
light reached your eye, this star
could have already disappeared, the same thing,
your consciousness with yours, if
your consciousness by the time you
heard it
speak or is no longer there, therefore, you
cannot be speaking or people approached
my lami, I translated it, I brought it into
English, probably English, people
ask, I constantly feel
depression and games.
He feels it himself, he feels depression,
sometimes people came from far away in
the summer to ask my lama about something and did
n't ask, "Lama, Lama, I'm depressed,
what are you doing?" He answers, "You
just need to be happy," and he returns to
his mantra, everything is clear, meaning that
everything is finished, and this person and I
are waiting for the continuation and
we are waiting, well, what should we do in this
depressed person, a Jew, commit suicide.
I told you what you need to do, that you should
be happy, and the person leaves, he is so angry
and depressed, angry. I go to the Rinpoche and
say to the Rinpoche, "Why did you tell this
person to be happy? Why didn't you
tell him to
do something? Something? Something? He answers, "It's too late,"
these thoughts are already planted, they have
already sprouted, it's too late to
change anything, he will already be that person in
depression today.
If he doesn't want to be depressed
next week,
then you need to treat other
people well this week, that's all. If you
treat people well this
week until next week, your thoughts
will be better. The same thing from meditation, you can do it.
Meditate you can't
control your consciousness you will
hear what comes out of your from the
seeds in your consciousness something may turn out
quietly something may turn out
noisy and
but who the moment since you already
heard it is too late race they say you
can't push a tree back into the
ground that guy who wandered
vipassana he said you can't
push a tree back into the ground it's
impossible and the real key meditation
is not disturbing other people to do so in order for
other people to be happy so that
they are calm and then
next week seven and when the opening with
your consciousness will be calm you
cannot control your consciousness it is
impossible because the light has already been and
lowered and the stars under and the moment you
listen to your thought it is already too late the
real key meditation is not
disturbing the consciousness of other people to be
helping people to be calm
happy and next week your
consciousness will be calm gas block what kind of
question if you feel fear
if some strange images leave
your consciousness time agitation
they were planted last week it is
too late to do something with them it is
how to say the light of the stars and how to talk
to a star that emitted light a hundred years
ago already  It's too late to talk to them,
you need to somehow make use of
all the results that have come to you,
learn to work with the four forces and
make sure not to scare people
now. If such bad thoughts are coming to you now,
this is a signal that
says that once in the past you
did something
unpleasant to other people. So, the second
part of the meditation
is the second part of the lion dance meditation.
So, let's imagine that we just left the
fourth level without form, we can
teach consciousness and when our thoughts
flew out of consciousness, we did not resist in any way
and now we are starting a
real meditation. The 9th floor is the
real meditation 1.8 including the zero
level. This is air conditioning.
This is not meditation. They do not resist
how a normal creature
perceives the world. Now,
imagine your teacher
in front of your consciousness.
Maybe it's your mother's or your
elementary school teacher. Maybe there is a
coach. Each of us had
some kind of coach with whom we felt
close. It could be your spiritual teacher,
like a priest or a fish or a monk. That
night, our professions can be imagined. You can
imagine
historical teachers. I will be Jesus
Moses Muhammad.
Your heart is a teacher.  This is especially important.
Someone who you think has helped you in
your life more than anyone else.
We call him Sergei, a teacher for
some of us,
if we haven't met anyone else, we
have some kind of feeling towards
someone
that he is my more serious teacher. You can
imagine your ideal
teacher of the heart and you can imagine
how the teacher is sitting in front of you right now.
This is the beginning of the ninth generation.
I ask you to make the teacher real.
This is not a picture, but wandering from the place.
You are a warm, breathing, living teacher
who is sitting next to you.
Knee, knee, your orders. The teacher's eyes are closed
and open, and he looks at you with
great love with a very strong emotion. I am
very happy that you are meditating.
There are many qualities of your teachers
that you admire there,
and the qualities that we would like to break down into
development for ourselves. That is why our teacher
and in this meditation at level 9 you choose,
but from these qualities, which one do you like? What do you
like about this person? Maybe it's
your child.
I know a person who said that his
wing breaks his dogs. I believed him and
think now about one good
quality that you admire in this
teacher.
You can give me a little  For every day if
you want meditation or maybe stay
with one teacher for 4 for
four or five days, then change and he is
another iPad is equal to the current, do imitation
more and more you will find
more good qualities there teachers are
not very useful to isolate negative
qualities in another person and imitate,
but this does not make you a better
person for inspired to inspire you to
choose the quality that you
admire
in someone else and
focus on it so choose
the quality
now direct your attention to the center of
consciousness where we meditated I
imagine a black room and in the center of
this room imagine a small
nest like a bird's nest and in this nest there
are six or seven and beautiful
silver faces as if a spotlight is directed at them
they are very bright sparkling
beautiful
rearrange how one of these eggs
opened and a picture came out a glowing
picture small maybe the size of a
small berry
and it opens up leaves this family
like a hologram
and this picture of your teacher your
quality of your teacher in my case, let's say
I think about caring we ox man
other people I imagine like this
silver egg  It
opens in the center of my consciousness, a
picture of care comes out of it
and we imitate it, it moves forward to the
front of my head and it leaves
my head and it is superimposed on
my lava which is in front of me like a
blanket and it is covered with it like this,
I see the care of my
teacher, if it is so comfortable, can
tell you how these seven times come from
your right now from your heart if you have a
tendency to be nervous during not ation,
you can shoot
pictures, it comes out from opposite the back at the
level of the navel and this will help you
ground yourself and the most important time of
vegetation
is I feel that what you see with
your teacher, those beautiful qualities in my
case, care, they come from seeds in
my consciousness, do not create pictures and these
pictures are superimposed on the head and
the virtue
that I see with you comes from
these seeds,
think about this
and then direct your attention to 2 eggs,
see how it opens,
see how the picture comes out which is
superimposed on your mother and this is the second
moment of care and again to the face and
repeat this process for several minutes
in real life this happens
sixty-five times per second
one with the other these eggs open 55
times in 1 second
now we slow down their process
If you do this part correctly,
otherwise the shocking feeling is that what
I see is the beauty that I see from my
teachers, all this comes from me, I may
not see this quality in myself, not the
seeds to see it in
another person,
and now we
[music]
will try to imagine what I did to
plant the seeds, I had to do what
if something from the sea in my world, I follow
some quality, my tormentors, it
must be that I somehow planted this
seed, it can be in this life, but we will
imagine that we can send our
past lives and try to imagine
what you did in a past life,
what you planted the seeds for and be
creative, be joyful,
it is something beautiful that you did, just some
very beautiful life, some kind of habits
that you had for many
years, then some kind of through other people and
the way, imagine something beautiful,
be creative,
don't limit yourself to anything,
imagine any story, come up with
your simple life, it may not be
entirely correct, maybe it
happened to them sometime in the future, you
will see passed lives directly, well, right
now, just do  some story
write your film about your past
life
what p it was maybe thousands of years from
maybe a hundred years ago, and in India or
Europe or I was an Indian
[music]
how I treated such people what I
did day after day what plant seeds
to see such a caring lama and so
write your story just how many
minutes then take a break
now or low with the names of which in
front of you now you have much
more and feeling why you will see this
quality from respectfully ask him to
move aside and now
imagine the
right image of your
lama which for also kaklama on the same
as the second husband in the kitchen this
second
imaginary lama his good qualities do
not come from me does not come from
my family I do not deserve him it does not come
from the fact that I did good
things to my people it's just an
accident I just met this lama
by chance he does not come from me there is no
history between us in the past there is no
one in a past life when I
planted the seeds for the meeting there is no
future between
such a beautiful ending of this story
there is no future in life together there are no
past and future in principle
We don't walk through lives, decay together,
it's just a coincidence,
I met him by chance, I came here
by chance, he was walking, what a coincidence, if you
follow this chain of
thought, everything is by chance, I meet
people by chance, there are no past
reasons for this, even the universe itself
came from some kind of sudden,
random explosion, Big Ben, some
grains were colliding with each other
billions and billions of times, and suddenly they
somehow joined together and created, but we
washed away, and with our eyes and shafts, we created
this world, and it's just some kind of big coincidence, chance,
it's such a random lama to God, lama,
random lama, lama from the Big Bang,
and try to feel how
wrong this is, my beautiful dear, I
still have the strength, and this is not
[music]
the production of a random Big Bang,
this does not mean, this is not true, that we have
from someone in the future, in a place where we spent a
lot of life, hurray, together, and it comes from these
beautiful seeds, I dedicate myself to this, I
deny this idea of ​​​​randomness, breaking, I do not
believe in it, and then erase this false
randomness  lama and bring
back the
real lama and be aware that
this is the place
where the real lama sits,
this is the place where
we sat down and the place from which we erased the
existing lama, and that is, emptiness
and this emptiness is needed so that
this lama can appear there and since your
dear lama exists in this
space
that remains 100 as we erased
this random lama, this lama of yours
exists in emptiness,
illuminate 3 long exhalations,
open your eyes, stretch, I will answer
questions after the break, we have a
15-minute break, I think there are
some delicious juices there in the kitchen,
I hope you drink a green drink, with
my point of view, in my category,
edit this green drink
is right after yoga, I
hate both, but if you drink it, and here is your
class, we will return to the stanza that
is at the end of the sutras, the diamond cutter, we have
about an hour, and closer to the end of the hour, we
will tell you about the schedule of your
meditations today,
please tell me, cockroach, dimmer,
depot, my
vegetable  There would be a dance club on video in
this Rostov
Sun Sky there we are on the word tarako which
means star that is and we said that it
can have six different
meanings I will repeat 3 that we went through the
first is what
master Kamala Shell and master Vas a Bandu
and what not Lama and John Seppo said and this
means that stars can only sit in the
dark and darkness means in their understanding
represents what we do not understand the
object if sda represents
bad things in our life because we do
not understand and
if we if we understood they would
go away disappeared as if the sun came out
we used the example of your husband or
your wife someone was upset when
he said about the husband and says the wife also has a
problem and war yelled at their
children last week then you
come home your husband yells at you for no
reason calling you a
stupid fool and you have two choices
either understand that they understand that they
come from that your husband comes like
your teacher from a small seed
or you can think that I
did nothing at all he just to so  I am
being treated badly if you think that you have
not done anything before then it is like
darkness and then my husband is like a star and he
will hurt you he will
harm you and we say that of
course I have to change the shift that
is we do not need to change my husband we
need to change a lot we do not need to
talk
this will not change my husband this does not mean that
someone you should allow someone to
harm you if someone hurts you you do not
need to just stand and say this is
just my family and allow
you to be hurt if you have to do something
you can leave you can
ask for help if it is
illegal you have to do what you
have to do but what you have to
understand will work for years or not this
happens seeds but you should not last
you you accept responsibility and you
say I have to leave now or I
have to seek help because of
legal help or for psychological
and here we have a very strict rule you
sign no alcohol no drugs no
nothing do not interfere with other people not for
me to pester people these are our rules
14 years and we have a process if something
if something happens to you what
if happens  then you are contacting the
circle, Vadik, the leadership, these people,
they are our leadership, fox
too, if something happened to you,
that someone here is treating you badly,
you can tell them if
you are embarrassed, you can write an
anonymous letter and we have a system
for investigating programs and this
system is 14 years old, I was at all the meetings, the
leadership is always this
matter, we investigate people, we have, we have
different questions, we had all sorts of
difficulties, we even
reported
people to the police, that is, if you have
any problems, please let us know
and even if you have an old problem, you
can still tell us about it, but
the stars are from you, but even if two stars come
from you, this does not mean
you do not need to go to the police or you do not
need, you just do not need to be angry and
you can fix it, this
means that by subjugating your seeds, you can
fix the whole situation, the second second
meaning of the word star, another teacher
says that hand over the truth of suffering
when the sun comes out that the sun for them
is a direct perception of the emptiness of
emptiness, that is, whoever sees the post
directly cannot have  suffering and will
never be able to gather more food
for suffering they may still have
old food that is hidden but they do not have
they do not plant new karma for
rebirth another person says
I have a different understanding this is emptiness
emptiness that allows things
to appear that is for him
darkness is not ignorance darkness is
emptiness
we just did a meditation where we
canceled the wrong
your random teacher remains like a
white white screen white screen in a
movie theater cancel the wrong shaft and
this creates space for the normal
real lama whips to
project that is according to this
person darkness means emptiness and
it allows things to arise for you like
stars for him everything appears to arise
well apparent because
because emptiness allows it like a
white screen in a movie theater and your mind is
like a projector and what pictures you
put there in your mind and you will
watch if there was no emptiness if there was
no screen there would be no things
if there was no black space then
the stars would have nowhere to shine this is the
third this is the third idea 4 now we are
ready for  4 the same
lama says therefore
darkness first in the first example
sutra diamond cutter it can
exist an element a
good thing not a bad thing that is necessary
bad or good
this misunderstanding is a good thing he
says you can think of emptiness as
good things or what is bad as when
we talk about misunderstanding darkness is
bad and then the star is your second husband
but you can think of it as useful
things as emptiness like a white screen and
without it we can have nothing this is the
fourth way how to understand stars in
the dark he says you know you can
think of mouth as bad and darkness
you can as good if you want to
go deeper this is the emptiness of darkness Milan
someone likes someone doesn't like how
it sounds on there it can be with ignorance
and it can be emptiness
that allows to arise to say to others
to manifest other things this understanding
number four understanding number five
comes from the guy
atari nagarjuna
very famous and war organizers of
Buddha
one of the first great areyas after
we finish Kamala power we will begin
his most famous book which is
called wisdom and  Then of course people
called her a very very long name but
he liked the short name
here are the enemies on the parameter of Karrik the
root text is
strictly at Nastya and he just 221
wisdom twenty-seven chapters all pf
poetry is very incredibly beautiful and it's like a
journey to the realm of Buddha and we
will we will study all this everything very much
and about emptiness in Tibet in China in India and
Nepal
Mongolia in Japan they all come from
Nagarjuna from this book you will have a
good time I think it will take two or three
years we will go through
I have never seen good translations in
any case Nagarjuna wrote a lot on
m but he also wrote comments there is a
famous prayer
called Samantha Badra prayer Samantha
Badra in this prayer the most common
offering is what is this from this
imagine that the sky is covered with flowers
and offer to the teacher this part is to
break this part for the match on Georgia
he wrote a commentary to that
famous prayer and there he talks about
how stars arise in a glass of water and
if you  Go out at night in that Montel and you
will not talk wholesale
only one understood you have a bucket of water
bucket and you can see the stars
reflected in the bucket of water and here
he says Nagarjuna says that stars
mean this means this is an illusion
the meaning of a star is an illusion it is just an
illusion because you doom you can
see stars in a bucket of water but it is not
real it is not
you can use this
app the app for stars on your
phone point it at a bucket of water
nothing happens and if you point it at a
real star then you will get the name
and history of the star this is number five nogat
wife says that a star is an illusion
because you can see all the stars in a
bucket of water
number six is ​​just an
ordinary ordinary meaning of stars they did not
change they are fickle
they go away every 12 hours they change you
can say that the 6th meaning of a star
is that they are fickle and they
go away all the time
one of the most famous questions about
this stanza
in history is whether he is talking about
impermanence or he is talking about
illusion because some of these 9 of these
metaphors they they  It seems very
clear that they talk about illusions,
they are constantly talking about impermanence, but sometimes it
seems to me that he is talking about illusions and from a
huge, huge question for 2000 years, did
Buddha talk about impermanence or was he
talking about illusions?
How would you vote depends on your
connection. I would vote like this. I
agree. Sorry, it's him. Both stars
come and go and
disappear, just like our relationships.
So our life is like our money, like our
body, they come and go, well, they
are also illusions, and this is an illusion,
it depends on the darkness of misunderstanding, and so
you are now ready
to evaluate meditation number 20,
we will begin with the ring of meditation number
twenty, the nature of things around us,
how much.
What are the first three about
what is the world like? The
first three of nine examples
describe the world. What is our world like? So far we've
only touched on one of the 27 meditations,
23 meditations, and we've only
touched on one third of the atomization. Maybe
for a few months you'll have to
stay here. The nature of things around
us is stars and a dark sky. And now we're
going to the second. What is the meaning of "te
mire te mire te mira" in Sanskrit?
Tell me, "Mira" is three roots. Here are three times. Core
Team. There are three. These are three meanings in
Sanskrit. One of them is darkness, and
in Russian,
darkness is darkness, dark
-dark, dark.
You see, in Russian,
the root is the same. This is what
blindness means. It can also mean
sticking together. What you see is
darkness. This
is the second meaning. So, to be
cut off. A
place in a village
that is separate from all other villages. For that, a temple.
For that, to pray. Temple. Temple
comes from this. Cut off
from team.
This is what you call a particle
that cannot be divided. I will give it away,
and there, that is, not  We divide and there is a
third meaning, this is fear, fear
timid, this comes from being shy,
being afraid, te mira, which means I'm alone, I
cut off, I'm blind and I'm scared, this is it, maybe
I'm cut off, I'm blind, I'm scared, this is ti
mira, this means in this case it's
cataracts, tour, I stroke, this is additional,
well, what makes you blind,
additional skin on the eye, and so
now I'll give you
6 by 7 and 6 different meanings for cataracts,
six different times, this cataract on the
eyes of the
younger one, your gang, why not us, but
dio less, they say, the main meaning
here is you think that there is something there,
but there is not, because of this cataract on the
eyes, you see something there, something that is
not there, it's only your cataract on the
eyes,
these are your problems with your eyes, just the
second baby looks as if he is
there, in fact, these are just problems with
your eyes,
this is the most famous definition of ti
mira cataracts, they always separate them
into two types, knows, meaning 1, the first, the first
meaning is always divided into
two, you see people and you  You see things
that aren't there, you see people, and to see
things that aren't there, your husband is people, but
for example, you're stuck in a traffic jam.
Someone calls me today and says, "I'll be late
today,
why?" But there's a traffic jam. I'm taking the traffic jam as a station.
FBU, and you can
talk about this in Shanghai or Berlin,
but here, oh my God, there's a traffic jam in a storm.
Well, next time you'll come up with a
reason for being late. But traffic jams,
they also come from you. Don't be angry at the
traffic, don't blame the traffic. The
reason for studying is to
stop getting upset about
things. We are all doing this. This is a
thorn in our side. No need to be
angry at
other people and at others and at things.
They all come from you. The
second meaning is this guy. He
says he likes to talk about truth and
suffering. I usually call it the fact of
suffering because it represents
suffering in itself. You can say, well, I
can say, four facts of suffering. He
says, if only you have this
[music], a
broken instrument, a broken
instrument of perception.
Only in this case can you see
suffering, that is, that  what again is
that your eye
and the Ori-Orii which looks at emptiness
directly they cannot perceive
suffering that is to say for him an
eyesore is suffering this is the truth of
suffering the second meaning if you did
not have an eyesore
you would not be able to see suffering
because Arya does not see suffering for
now and while he is in the perception of emptiness
directly the third meaning
this person he says let's
talk about Chandra Kersey let's
go back to the entry into the middle path a
very famous book about emptiness what is the
middle path in Chandra Hertz who
can tell me this book by Nagarjuna
Chandra Hertz
book in the attic RDI this is one of the most
famous books about the darkness of emptiness
14 ago it is called entry into the
middle path we are talking about wisdom in a
book on gadgets which is called
wisdom or the middle path in his book
he says he talks about a famous
example from ancient times for things
that you see
that come from you and an example like for
example Hersha Michael taking a shower of your
bath Skin Scott recognizes all the time
340 hairs remain on  There on the floor you
can see hair if I don't clean up after
myself then hair remains and Chandra Gertie
says but some people have a scratch
on their eye and they see a lot of hair and
take time trying to wash and
clean Adam hair no it's all about
scratches on the eyes that's the third third
meaning of the problem the third problem with the
eyes is that you will see what
you have seeds for and this is the first
law of karma what is the first law of karma what
before all this watermelon makes the fight creates the
watermelon what your eyesore in
makes you see it matches what
you recently did to others that is you 200
because you have a thin
scratch on your eye if you see someone
screaming you already yes because you
yelled at your children last week
and the scratch in
your eye in a dream will match what you
see what is in the illusion the content of the
illusion will be about how you treated
other people last week
last month that
is the eyesore will decide what
you see you hurt someone
you hurt someone on  They screamed and next
week the hair that you see
in the bathroom, which is actually a
scratch on the eye, will match
what you did last week
when you talk about a defect in the eye,
you will see this scratch, you
will see what you did
last week, well, that
is, it is not an accident, it always
matches what you did last
week if you talked last
week about how beautiful they are,
what can you say when you come in and
I am such a beauty, you understand, this is also a
scratch on the eye, yes, this scratch is also
on the eye,
meaning number four is important for
this person, it is called confirmation,
it means what happened, what would happen
if a person without scratches on the
eye entered the room, what would happen if
clearly with a
clear look entered the room in the willows,
you enter the room, you open the door
and your husband tells you, you are a fool, from a thing
without reason, I did to you, what did you do to
me, mouth and in your friend enters
who just arrived from to baby 4,
they enter the room and you tell you,
can you believe
who someone called you Dora, I don’t
see anyone, but he  Here is my my husband and he yells
at me saying that I'm stupid
no I don't see anything I haven't done anything yet well
where is he he'll hide yes there he is
standing right in front of us I don't
see anything today says your friend you understand the one who
understands convulsions earlier to Almazda enters the
kitchen right behind you and they say I don't
see any husband this husband
whom I didn't do anything
someone without scratches and on the eye enters over
horrors the same kitchen doesn't see this
husband who I'm through this case this is
confirmation this is important for two
guys the
fourth meaning of scratches if the
person who if the person who is
standing next to
him has unbroken eyes there is no cataract on the
eye then he will tell you there is no
hair on the floor that is like the
heart itself beating my heart I don't
see any kind of husband here who is not my fault
this is the story of every interview with
students hundreds of times a year I talk to
people people tell me we have
problems no one listens
every year I talk to hundreds of hundreds of
people I will buy myself a voice recorder four steps
try maybe it is because of you
I am with
My husband talked to 1000 thousand people like this I know about the
four steps but my husband is different he is different
I say tell me about my
husband I don't have this karma I do
n't even know their husband I don't have scratches on my
eye and that's why they come to me I have
other scratches with their
own but I don't have the same
exact scratch as you I tell him
can I can advise you that is it's like
crazy not crazy when I
go when I go to my teacher then I'm
crazy he's not crazy he doesn't have
and they tell me yes not yours your husband seems like a
nice guy no I understand that about a
friend about others it suits other people
but no they are about me this is
called confirmation how much we have
gone 4 number 5
your gang master our gang
he says think about the
wheel of life by the way how do you prepare to
think about the wheel of life you
do the lion dance that's why the
dance of freedoms was taught why Buddha gave very
she danced Dmitry Maitreya
use the dance lion dance and
go straight to the forest of life this is the coolest thing the
wheel of life in our case it is  Watch
how the seeds unfold in dependent
origination usually in the wheel of life everything is
mixed up all these people everything that is in
the wheel of life is suffering this is about the cause of
death and we are shackled to enter
this is important what the master says you
abandon says if your your pair
equipment your sense organs they if
they were created by karma then they are
broken
they are defective very interesting your
telescope is scratched
your telescope and all these your
sense organs they were built they were
built with scratches a normal
person cannot feel anything without
error we were born with these
scratches on our eyes on our ears on everything that
we perceive everything with an error at this
nature of man a
natural condition to
perceive everything incorrectly all the time it is
only and only with a very large dose of
perfect wisdom we can
perceive anything correctly because
we were with defects with those who lived from the factory
we were born with these defects
because they were created by incorrect
thoughts and effective thoughts in our
nose eyes ears it was all created by a
blind person not an ordinary person
who did not study he is obliged to perceive
reality incorrectly this is very  A
deep Buddhist thought is not just a
mistake in your consciousness.
Your equipment is broken. You
cannot see that things
come from you. You were born this way.
You were born, and after 5 years
you see that things come from you by
themselves. You were born this way. It's like a
cookie, a new lollipop,
as if Sakharnov's cookies are
actually sweet. They come from you,
but your language, and your language, it
was built with ignorance. Defects. With a
defect, it tells you that the cookie is
sweet. No, it's not true. There are no sweets there.
Cookies. Sweets come from you.
You see, your equipment is broken.
This is what it says. In particular, ice number 5,
named number 5.
And so now good news number 6
is not only all the bad news
number 6. Labor, but Burman,
Nick must, and Adam must learn, and
Seiji, but Burova, Luke, on the test, ravine, south
to south, which means this part is part of
your consciousness, the mind
that cannot be removed. This is when
stage 4 cancer is
removed, then you will die. You have cancer, you
come to the doctor.  And the doctor tells you, you
say, can the cancer be removed? They tell you,
no, you already have metastases all over your body, they'll
have to remove your entire body.
It's spread all over your body, it's
now part of you, we can't, it can't be
removed. This isn't windows and nowhere, this
means metastases, cataracts, which with
metastases can't be removed without
destroying the eye. But Burova
means it's on top, under any, which
means that if you have a good
surgeon, it
can be removed normally. This isn't
Baburova's vision. This is understanding
number six, he says, that it can be removed,
that your
cataract is only superficial, it's
not a part of you, it's removable, it's
operable, but it's gotten to you. It can't be
removed yet, through meditation, teachings, and
your efforts.
You can remove it,
and you will see things. Did you understand correctly?
These are 6 understandings. We're going to
Depo VIP. It's a long time, and
Deppa Deppa Deppa Deppa
in the poem should be about Minion, and
because the next one is sunny and has
consonants, well, this is Depo
stages, then it's easy. The root means to shine. Where is the
PPV network, and B, they change among themselves.
[music]
Amazing.
Virgo, that is, there are many names of the gods of dust,
this Jove, she is from this, the
seeds from the gods, they come from whose
root is
Jupiter, Jupiter is the father of light, Jupiter, his
name was not Deus,
and so it comes from this, where the father is
not heaven, and a lot of
Zeus, Zeus, didi
and Thursday also occur, Tuesday, Tuesday, Tuesday,
this comes from a person who, in
general, the one who lives in heaven, until his
wonderful day, day, even Zeus, Jupiter, and of
they all come from this root, where it
shines like a halo, says Kamala sewed,
by the way, how much is the meaning of 6 here, too, 1,
you, your gang, Kamala sewed,
what does not break, guy,
they say the same thing, to light this
oil lamp,
you need two things: the wick and them, and
oil or wax.
These two things to make a lamp: the
wick and the fuel. Something must feed the
fire, which is fire. Fire is your
consciousness, this is your incorrect, your
sensory awareness. This is
wrong, and which is from the factory defects with
defects, perception. This light, light
perception, is what you  You turn on the second
level of the formless sphere of meditation.
This light that you turn on
is yours, and your awareness that
feeds it. The wick represents this karma. The wick is this karma.
Kamala Shila says, this is a piece of
cloth, a piece of cloth, a sifter of
oil or wax. This is the wheel of life
number eight. Who is this, what is it? Is it
so bad yet? 8. 8 link of the wheel of life. You
want money, you want it, and you extend your
hand. Someone sends you
money from Guangzhou, and you
have two choices: pay taxes or not. Nobody
knows what you received.
Someone gives you cash for some service in
America. You have to pay taxes, but you
think, well, nobody knows about that. I'll
just spend the money. I'll just use the
money. I don't have to pay taxes. You
understand, this behavior,
this desire. This
will be karmic 7, and a
misunderstanding of where the
money comes from, and the desire that comes from
this,
this misunderstanding. It will be karma, what is the
opposite
for good 7, or what will be
good? You
need to share money, coffee, meditation.  rejoice need to rejoice about
good things good deeds case of good good
karma
wick is giving money to someone
oil rejoice I'll finish drinking like
I did it admit to be happy I'm
happy that I will do your gang says that like this
depo
lamp 3 3 example and at 9 the wick is karma
be generous give money to other people
oil is cafe meditation correct
behavior
I'm happy that I did a good thing I
ha I'm happy that I did this with these
two you will have a fire from bad karma
absolutely the same way you lie about your
taxes this is don't pay me hide
your income in delta in the wick and
and rejoice that I succeeded and this
is oil without oil not
very strong food it turns out you
can light it but it will burn out very quickly you
need fuel and fuel is a misunderstanding of where the
money comes from everything is good we
can continue this
guy says
let's connect this what he keeps
saying she wants a question about Denmark from time to
time say let's connect this to
suffering the wick is a material
cause
what material cause is that things
become  Others,
what is 7 for a tree, that is, and
turns into a tree, that is, time 7
will stop, that is, this is a material
cause, a direct cause, a
thing in a seed
becomes a tree, but
additional causes contribute: water,
sunlight, and all sorts of fertilizers,
Karamba says, the
material cause is a wick for
memory, for a flame, a wick, and
additional causes are oil, and they both
represent
suffering, this gives fire to suffering, which
means that this was with whom I was talking,
I think I said, her house and that of her
friends burned down in California.
6 thousand houses burned down in California. This is
not cheap. These houses are expensive. These people
can
afford them. In general, it was such a
superficial fire that no one
can stop. With a strong
wind, the treetops are overflowing.
Understanding number two is downloaded. If you
have a material cause of bad karma, and
if you have this, I'm glad I
did it.
You regret it, but I didn't pay
taxes. Yes, you're kidding. I
saved the money. This is bad behavior.
It's like a chip. This is
what multiplies for him. We  We
did this, we do this for one circus for
several thousand, we light the lamp,
twist the wicks, we prepare for a very long time,
and you, what you learn to do quickly, you
learn
not to put them together because
they can catch fire, and that
is, they need to be laid out all the time,
otherwise they will catch fire and burn
your house to the ground, this is
his understanding, I'll
stop here now I want to go through
your schedule, we will and we will stop,
and so, excuse me, I think, what about
10 10 30, let's continue giving and he still has
half an hour, we will stop at 10:20, we will stop, and we have
another 20 minutes, everyone is happy, key
number three, understanding about the lamp,
three with a knife, it's more difficult when we
talked about the stars,
and the star, we talked about darkness, darkness, to
emptiness, and light is what you
see, in order for you to see the star, light, you
need this, like a screen, dark, dark, and
[music] the
basis is emptiness, there is only if the world is
empty,
you can see things only if you
have a white screen on which to project,
you can  Business cards, that is, you
need this emptiness for the basis in the
Odessa language of terms, home is the
emptiness that is the basis and
these things that you saw into cataracts are
we everywhere things that were not there we
thought when he says to reach from the moment
about the lamp he says that
but this is what you think people
things light lamp in this case are pulled out
of the context of emptiness and says so much about
it
why I see things people this is how
seeds open without without voids and
because the world seems to come to meet
because this word is the
same in Tibetan as lamp
which what technically it is deceptive I
really desserts reality is
deceptive reality why because
it deceives you it seems as if it is like this in
water towards you
arises in total for all your
senses your nose was defective from the factory
even the nose says oh look this guy
didn't wash today in the wrong place you are you
just did not observe sexual purity that is
why this guy did not grind did not
wash this what is this what is
telling you something is happening from the guy do not
ask  If you respect the
attitude of other people all the time, then everyone
around will wash. The
third meaning of the lamp
means that the world is happening like this on the
oncoming aria. Aria
is for those who saw emptiness directly and the
name is what people are called who do not yell and
subd for varieties of
people who see things as
arising by themselves. My husband
yelled at me. I didn't know anything. Words for
these for non-areans.
Incoming, entering, incoming observer, that
is, the one who sees how a thing happens to him. Then
somehow Anglin is the third
meaning of the lamp.
People see for a long time. Things happen from there by
themselves. I can continue.
Well,
it's difficult, but you had
difficulties before. That's why you came here.
And mountain is Nagarjuna
and Conchita. We are ready. Things are empty, but they
work. Things are empty, but they work. That
is, in fact, you can say I
would kiss you.
Your husband will get angry and my partner will get upset at me
too. The sensor will be upset about things. Posts, but
they work. If there is a cause and conditions,
they will work. And if there is a
cause and
conditions, we say aspirin. We
call it aspirin. 10
aspirin. What is the function?  Spirin suppresses and
relieves headaches. What's inside it? The
active ingredient is a
cycle oxygenase
2 inhibitor. It stops nerve
transmission of pain. That's what it's called. The
active ingredient is a cyclooxygenase 2
inhibitor. Where are the two of us? Ask.
Can you trust the Canadian brand?
It works. Sometimes it works. Sometimes it does
n't work. Sometimes it means they still have
n't found the true cause. Sometimes it
means it doesn't work. You won't get on the
plane.  If it sometimes works and sometimes
fails, but you take aspirin, which
sometimes works, sometimes doesn't, what does it mean
that the active ingredient is sometimes inactive?
We can say so, sometimes the active
ingredient is this, that's what they should call it.
When aspirin works, what is the active
ingredient? Your seed,
your seeds, because you
helped someone who had a headache last
week and you have seeds for the cycle for
heterocycle oxygenase 2,
because this inhibitor is not an
active ingredient.
Your karma is the active ingredient.
So this guy says, look,
you mix oils and a wick and
fire together, it will work, but this all
comes from you. It's empty, empty,
why is it empty? The inhibitor that
works is very, very, very quiet.
When you're so quiet, I think you don't
understand anything. Okay, it's your seeds
that make them process.
It's your seeds that activate the ingredient.
If there is a contradiction between emptiness and the lamp,
emptiness gives the lamp a place to
be. Emptiness means
fire doesn't burn. It doesn't burn by itself.
Fire burns by itself because you have karma. The
higher school of Buddhism says.
Heat is part of fire,
moisture is part of water. Well, high school
says no. Who put heat in a fire, heat from a skating
rink? You can take moisture from
water and systems. We believe that Jesus walked
on water. It's all about seeds. If you
have seeds, then you.
If there are any
contradictions between Buddhism and
Christianity, Jesus spoke of 17 all
day, evil days. A sign that you understand
emptiness. This means you are more successful in
your life,
financially, in relationships, your health, in your
state of mind, the state of your world. These
five things come from you. This
signifies that you understand emptiness. This
means that you can make things
happen. You see, it's not like that.
Emptiness is what you're doing. I'm posing.
Emptiness
is a sign of a person who doesn't understand
simplicity. You see, someone who understands
emptiness. He's like the one
sitting in the movies. He's very interested. He wants
life to be cool. He wants everything to be
cool and wonderful. They know how to sow
seeds because they know that everything is empty. Empty
means nothing. It doesn't
come from seeds. The last two are
number four, now number 5.
This person wants you to
understand. He's a little bit.  Agrees with Haram
Pai, says that what's below, don't forget
that good things only also happen.
Seeds in Buddhist terminology and in the
term, feet laid to torment. We'll get there
if you understand the cause of samsara, the
cause of nirvana. They are the same principles.
All the problems of your life and
all the successes of your life come from the
same principles. From the causes of
seeds, oil and wick, fire. This is number
five. Good and bad things come from
your seeds. Number four was 4. There was a thing that
works, although not beads and empty. Number five is
good things, bad things. They come
from you. They are searched. And in the Odessa language, you
would say the calendar is
core. This means samsara is such a ring of
life. This is nirvana.
They both come from 1 principle. The
highest good and the highest evil. They come
from the same principles. He, yes, by the way, the
correct pronunciation is samsara, not
hosanna, sara, before before, from
Sanskrit. And if someone says "I'll
strangle you myself," then you'll see. In
raw Sanskrit, before the s,
the number changes and it's not a big wheel.  Somewhere
far away, tell me the moment when you
give, when you start the wheel of life
in the kitchen, at what moment when you
say no, you're a fool, here you
transplant the
uncles behave badly, you call them
stupid children,
you hear yourself, you sow 7 and then it
comes and
your husband tells you you're a fool, and at
that moment you can, you can
stop the blind man, or you can
continue the wheel, how do you continue the
wheel, no, yes, you're a fool, and then he
will behave badly again, this is a
mini samsara,
don't think that samsara is some kind of huge
wheel, at birth we will make samsara
a thousand times at once, our reaction to
problems, it spins the wheel again and
again, no, you're a fool, I don't know why
children behave like this, his children are rude, what's
happening to my husband, he
calls me a fool all the time, this is how you
spin the wheel and the root of samsara and the
root of nirvana, these are the same principles,
Deppa lamp, Deppa
Tara world map, you will drown tomorrow
again,
right and  That's right, in relation to
do it,
be nice, you can sing it
tomorrow. It's so addictive. It gets attached at
home. Listen to them
once, but you won't be able to forget the saints. Then it will always
be spinning in your head. The
melody is very addictive. Okay, so we'll
do it after meditation because if
you do it at home, subsidies are available. They knew how to do it for you. They will
destroy everything.
That melody will always be spinning in your head. After
class, someone will sleep in Chinese. No, and
Stanley, can you find someone?
I learned some beautiful
Chinese melody that will
stay in your head for a long time. For Chinese
translation, and then we will memorize both Chinese
and Sanskrit. I want
to remember how many we've covered in Chinese. Number
six is ​​easy. This movement could. There's a
famous metaphor. When they learn words, a
metaphor is
said to be a candle. Compare this. If
you say life is like a candle, there's a comparison.
And if you say life is a candle, then there's a
metaphor. What does that mean? It burns to
the ground. Believe me, I'm looking
at the dish all the time. Every minute it burns to the
ground. That's not it.  constancy is the
last meaning of an oil lamp. Just
remember that life is a candle.
Every minute you lose. You
were born a bit cartel and your life
costs you 65 seeds per second and it
goes away like a candle burns to the ground.
It's obvious but no one talks about it. No one
mentions
it. I came up with it myself.
We covered three
metaphors, 3 out of 9. The
first three are related to what the world
around us is like.
What is the world like? It's like a star. It's like a
cataract. It's like a lamp. It's like a candle.
We finished the first large group of 9.
How many groups are there? Four groups. We are in the
second group. How many is there? In the second one,
one there's only this maia maia maia
maia.
Here is the root. The
root of this word. Usually, people are not
sure. In general, I'm not sure here. We may
be this and I, how can I be wrong? It may
be magic. High power. To confuse you. Magic, how can I
be wrong? Let's go. In Sanskrit,
exit is the exit. It's the past tense. Oh,
Maria. That is, it may be wrong. Nobody
knows for sure. May means illusion.
There are two large meanings here.  In
Buddhism,
illusion can mean that you think
you are looking at something that is not there, and
usually in the study of perception,
illusion can have many causes, one of the reasons is
Ilya and reasons, for example, very strong
emotions when you are angry or you are jealous,
you see things that are not there, what is it
called when things around you are
moving, if you have Astana, I
stop, cause an illusion of
movement when two cars are parked
opposite each other and suddenly they
drive away and it seems to you that you are about to
fall, go, in fact,
it is just this is just movement around
you, is this an illusion, is this why
strong emotions 2 1 time
May teaching May Buddhism by the way, what is the name of the mother's mother
in Buddhism May is
magical, but a magical trick we will be
his friend's mother of Buddha my we talked about
mother well, these magical
ideas, and when
when a rabbit is pulled out of a hat or
there is a coin behind the ear and so on, these are the
magical ideas of May when
you drive through the desert and see water
ahead, this illusion or when you have
whales magical ideas can
be something each other one of  these May and we'll
talk tomorrow I'll give you 9 messages
illusions tomorrow 9 meaning of illusion
and now let's talk about how you will
meditate what you need to do besides
sleep jet lag give I'll look
at the schedule and so you need to leave
here and have breakfast at the cottage
Veronica made me a super super
breakfast at 145
112 15 times you rest you can't
meditate
if you haven't slept enough forget
about it no it won't work it can't be
that you will meditate I made 12
rows conducted doesn't work if you didn't get enough
sleep if you need to sleep sleep
any time today if you need to
sleep just sleep stand
and meditate after you poured a
glass of cold water on your head but
if you didn't sleep last night or you
have jet lag then sleep
I'm ordinary I have rules for jet lag
and every frequent
traveler I have so many miles that I
recently sent a limo so that I have a
limo to take me to the next
plane to the next  My advice to the neighboring Kate:
If you have jet
lag, don't
go to bed until evening, hold out,
and then you'll get on schedule. But at home,
you'll have to come back again.
But usually, if you haven't slept before,
sleep
and do maybe Shamas food and after
sleep longer. Oil of
nicknames of all releases speaks of the amoeba knot itself.
If
yoga is for an hour, here's the calculation: this is a mixture and
Shavasanas. Not 2015.
Go through these three images: a
star, a cataract, and a lamp. Try keeping a
list of six words in
front of your eyes. You can
peek with your left eye. This is for luck. You can peek like this. There's a
bird that
looks like this with one eye. You can
peek about six qualities, six
meanings.
Try remembering the necks of meanings and
try to think about something real.
Your life's star, which is an illusion, is
my husband, who doesn't hurt.
Yesterday he hurt every time you
do something. Do imitation. Connect.
Connect with your life every day. No
need to philosophize. Think about the people in
your life who are like stars.
Think about moments.  There was a
cataract in your life.
Think about things that are empty, but they
work like a lamp, like aspirin. 55/15.
We will walk and look through the deputies.
You are a good knight. Conduct element 515.
Take a walk here, there is a very beautiful sunset.
Use a hat and sunscreen.
4 to 5 out of 7.
You can also practice the first 8
levels, or
should I do this once first? 1/8.
Complete either
level 9 or 9, or 1/8. Tomorrow
we will do the first two parts of the
lion dance, and we will go down together. There are
generally 5 parts in the lion dance. Today, there is a
lot of dust.
So, during meditation, 4 to 5 or from
12 to 1 o'clock, I drain. Do you want to warm up and
do what you can, but don't
overdo it. Always take water. No
one leaves the desert without water.
Never, never, never go out. I
always take a bag, a bag of our shoulders, your
hands are free, and always stay within
sight of your home. I
once got lost here for 5 hours, wandered around and
couldn't find you, and I lived here for seven years.  so
it can be dangerous don't go far keep
within sight of
your house
and don't wander after it
gets dark
snakes love twilight why because
mice love death why merge
energies because
everything here starts at the same time and you are
still walking 100 don't step don't
step where you are looking once a
man stepped over a ravine and there was a
snake in general if you are bitten by a
snake sit down and call this on the
exit with the Internet when when you run the
poison spreads faster so
relax and we can take you to the hospital they will
give you an injection everything will be fine if you
hear the snake it says please do
n't look at it come back
and many give looks mine what is it
they don't want you to be stepped on
some say look I'm here don't step
you they don't want you to eat too
big
you are big for them they are not stupid if you
step on them
they will fall apart but overall they are very
calm
Nobody in the desert bothers you
except people at 6
before your baby or the next one, do
two, then 8:30 after dinner, it's useless,
and it's time for meditation. Do a light meditation,
gratitude,
make a list of who helped your
life, a lot of people helped you without your mother, your
consciousness, your mind, thank you, the
safe, by the way, is large,
expanded on imitation. I like to drink
hot chocolate,
sit in a comfortable chair, forget about the pillow,
presentations. I like to sit on the porch
and look at the stars. You can read mantras. I used to
lie in the hall on the roof looking at the
stars and looking for shooting stars. I
read a million mantras there.
Take a chair, put on a sweater and
enjoy the stars. You will hardly
see them anywhere in the world. A match is far
from the city. The main thing during the third is
funk. Enjoy yourself, don't make
Jehovah, so smile. I hate
yoga. The most common mistake is that
people try too hard, don't try too hard, don't.
You can't meditate. If
you're putting in too much effort, if
you're tired, rest.